Little Dixie is a action, crime, thriller film directed by John Swab.
Erstwhile Special Forces operative Doc Alexander is asked to broker
a truce with the Mexican drug cartel in secrecy.
When Oklahoma Governor Richard Jeffs celebrates the execution of a high-ranking cartel member
on TV, his Chief of Staff and Doc inform him about the peace he just ended.
But it’s too late, as Cuco, the cartel’s hatchet man, has set
his vengeful sights on Doc’s daughter Dixie.
Doc Alexander, played by Frank Grillo.
Governor Richard Jeffs, played by Eric Dane.
Billie Riggs, played by Annabeth Gish.
Julie Reed, played by Mercedes Mason.
Karl Roach, played by Peter Greene.
Raphael 'Cuco' Prado, played by Beau Knapp.
Little Dixie is a 2023 American crime thriller film
written and directed by John Swab.
It stars Frank Grillo, Eric Dane, Beau Knapp, Annabeth Gish, Peter
Greene, Thomas Dekker, Mercedes Mason, and Maurice Compte.
The film premiered at the 2023 International Film Festival Rotterdam, and was released in select
theaters and video on demand in the United States on February 3, 2023, by Paramount Pictures.
The tone is emotional and intense.